divisiond.com 2015-06-17

# Privacy - Division-D

This Privacy Policy pertains to the Division-D website — www.divisiond.com — and is applicable to all users that visit the site.

The website is used for providing business information to prospective clients and business partners. It also serves as a marketing vehicle for Division-D. Division-D is committed to respecting your privacy and conducting business matters that follow all policies as required by law. Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated. This policy is effective as of January 1, 2011, but may change periodically to reflect any changes in legal requirements, company procedures, company products, service offerings and/or technology.

**Collection of “PII” (Personally Identifiable Information)**  
Personally identifiable information is only collected when you choose to provide it to Division-D, such as in an email or by completing a form on the website. The site does contain a contact page where you can contact Division-D personnel and request additional information. This PII may include: name, company name, address, telephone number or email address. This information is only used by Division-D to contact you in response to your inquiry, conduct business activities with you, provide customer service and provide new products and services to existing and prospective customers. You can request the individual information that Division-D has collected about you, correct factual inaccuracies in information, remove personal information and/or update your personal information by contacting privacy@divisiond.com. While Division-D may use the information it collects to notify you of necessary changes to the website, new services/offerings and unique opportunities, you can contact Division-D at any time if you do not wish to receive these notices by emailing Division-D at privacy@divisiond.com

**Third-party websites**  
Division-D is not responsible for the methods by websites or applications that contain links on the website or are linked to its website nor the contact and information presented therein. Third-party Internet sites and services accessible through Division-D have separate privacy and data collection practices, independent of Division-D. Division-D has no responsibility or liability for these independent policies or actions.

**Disclosure/Sharing of “PII” (Personally Identifiable Information)**  
Disclosure of personal information is not shared with anyone outside of Division-D, unless specifically stated otherwise. Division-D does not sell, rent or lease such personal information collected on the site to non-affiliated third parties without your consent. If data is being collected and/or maintained by any company other than Division-D or an agent for Division-D, you will be notified prior to the time of the data collection or transfer.

Division-D may share voluntarily-provided personally identifiable information (i) to enable third party service providers to assist or facilitate in the services Division-D provides; (ii) to comply with applicable laws and regulations or to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other lawful request for information Division-D receives, whether or not a response is required by applicable law, and to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of the Terms of Access, or as otherwise required by law; (iii) to enforce an agreement or to protect Division-D’s rights; with any parent, affiliated or successor entity; (iv) in connection with any asset sale, transfer, divestiture or liquidation; (v) in connection with strategic alliances, partnerships or other business arrangements to permit the offering of products or services Division-D believes may be of interest to you or where Division-D has determined that the information will be used in a responsible manner by the third party; or (vi) as permitted under any agreement with you. Division-D may also share aggregated data with others. Aggregated data does not include personally identifiable information. Except as provided Division-D will not share any of your information with any third party without your permission.

**Collection of “Non-PII” (Non-Personally Identifiable Information) and Cookies**  
This website uses Google Analytics to help analyze how users use the site. The tool uses “cookies,” which are text files placed on your computer, to collect standard Internet log information and visitor behavior information in an anonymous form. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including IP address) is transmitted to Google. This information is then used to evaluate visitors’ use of the website and to compile statistical reports on website activity for Division-D.

We will never (and will not allow any third party to) use the statistical analytics tool to track or to collect any Personally Identifiable Information (PII) of visitors to our site. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. Neither we nor Google will link, or seek to link, an IP address with the identity of a computer user. We will not associate any data gathered from this site with any Personally Identifiable Information from any source, unless you explicitly submit that information via a fill-in form on our website.

**Opt Out**  
If you do not want to store this information in your browser, you can easily deny, or opt out of, cookies. There is more than one way to opt out of cookies: manually delete your cookies by following the instructions contained in the “Help” section of your browser; or go to our ad server, ZEDO’s, opt-out page: http://www.zedo.com/tools/zedo_optout.cgi. Click the “Opt Out Now” button provided. We will no longer deliver ads targeted to your preferences and usage patterns. The ZEDO Opt-out Tool is cookie-based. In order for the Tool to work on your computer, your browser must be set to accept third party cookies. If you buy a new computer, change web browsers or delete this cookie, you will need to perform the opt-out task again.

We partner with ZEDO, a third-party ad server, and they are a member of the of the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI), a cooperative of online marketing and analytics companies committed to building consumer awareness and establishing responsible business and data management practices and standards. The NAI provides a mechanism to opt out of its member networks here: http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp

**Children Information**  
Division-D is respectful and keenly aware of the privacy rights of children. Division-D’s products and services are not intended for persons under 18 years of age and the website is not directed to children. Division-D does not knowingly solicit or collect any PII from children under the age of 18, nor knowingly markets Division-D products and services to children under this age. If you are a parent and are aware that your child has provided Division-D with PII without your knowledge or consent, please contact us immediately at [privacy@divisiond.com](mailto:privacy@divisiond.com)

**Security Measures**  
Division-D uses appropriate measures to ensure the security of all information, including the use of passwords, firewalls, encryption and remote servers, and routinely evaluate our practices to identify security threats or opportunities for the improvement of our services. No transmission of information is guaranteed to be completely secure. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise data security. You acknowledge and agree to assume this risk when communicating with us.

**Other Notices**  
We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time in the future. Please note that the use of information that we gather is subject to the privacy notice in effect at the time of use.

**Contact**  
If you have any questions or concerns about your privacy in connection with this policy, please send us a thorough description to [privacy@divisiond.com](mailto:privacy@divisiond.com) and we will try to resolve it. You may also contact us at 573-445-3083 or by mail at:

Division-D  
3806 Buttonwood Dr. Suite 100  
Columbia, MO 65201
